<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HCL CDC</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="java">Java is an object-oriented programming language with a built-in application programming interface (API) that can handle graphics and user interfaces and that can be used to create applications or applets.</string>
    <string name="ajava">Advanced Java is a comprehensive study of many advanced Java topics. These include assertions, collection classes, searching and sorting, regular expressions, logging, bit manipulation, serialization, threads, networking with sockets, Remote Method Invocation and Java Database Connectivity.</string>
    <string name="clang">C is a popular and widely used programming language for creating computer programs. Programmers around the world embrace C because it gives them maximum control and efficiency. C compilers are available for the majority of available computer architectures and operating systems.</string>
    <string name="data">A database is a collection of information that is organised so that it can easily be accessed, managed and updated. The data is typically organised to model relevant aspects of reality in a way that supports processes requiring this information.</string>
    <string name="moff">This is a suite of products developed by Microsoft Corporation that includes Microsoft Word, Excel, Access, Publisher, PowerPoint, and Outlook. Each program serves a different purpose and is compatible with other programs included in the package. The suite of programs is compatible with both the Windows and Macintosh operating systems. Microsoft Office is the most common form of software used in the western world.</string>
    <string name="php">PHP is a server-side scripting language that is used to develop Dynamic Web Applications. Its simplicity and lots of frameworks built around it make it a favourite choice for application developers.</string>
    <string name="android">Android is an open source mobile operating system that was developed and launched by Google. Over the years, Android has taken the lead in the number of phones the operating system is installed in. The creation of millions of android-based devices has resulted in a huge demand for developers well-versed with Android application (app) development knowledge</string>
    <string name="cpp">C++ is a general purpose programming language that is free-form and compiled. C++ is one of the most popular programming languages and is implemented on a wide variety of hardware and operating system platforms.</string>
    <string name="sql">SQL is a language to request data from a database, to add, update or remove data within a database or to manipulate the metadata of the database.</string>
    <string name="net">In this world of collaboration, .NET allows developers the flexibility of interacting through various interfaces such as Desktops, Phones, TVs, Browsers, Internet, etc. In fact, .NET is a platform that allows a developer to make intelligent applications with interoperability across platforms, that too in a limited timeframe.</string>
    <string name="asp">ASP.NET is a server-side Web application framework designed for Web development to produce dynamic Web pages. ASP.NET is a unified Web development model that includes the services necessary to build enterprise-class Web applications with a minimum of coding.</string>
    <string name="cjava">Java is a general-purpose, concurrent, class-based, object-oriented computer programming language that refers to the core or basic concepts of the Java programming language. It supports object-oriented concepts such as encapsulation, inheritance, multi-threading, exception handling and other basic features of java that comes as part of the Java standard edition forms Core Java. Core Java is the basic foundation for all advanced java technologies.</string>
    <string name="lamp">The acronym LAMP refers to first letters of the four components of a solution stack-Linux, Apache, MySQL and PHP, Composed entirely of free and open-source software, it is suitable for building high-availability heavy-duty dynamic Web sites and capable of serving tens of thousands of requests simultaneously.</string>
    <string name="vb">Visual Basic .NET (VB.NET) is an object-oriented computer programming language , an evolution of the classic Visual Basic (VB), implemented on the .NET Framework. VB.NET is a multi-purpose computer programming language from Microsoft that is suitable for most development needs. The language is designed with Rapid Application Development in mind, providing several tools to shorten development time.</string>
    <string name="electronics">Electronics deals with electrical circuits that involve active electrical components such as vacuum tubes, transistors, diodes and integrated circuits and associated passive interconnection technologies. Commonly, electronic devices contain circuitry consisting primarily or exclusively of active semiconductors supplemented with passive elements.</string>
    <string name="desktop">A desktop computer is a personal computer in a form intended for regular use at a single location desk/table due to its size and power requirements. The most common configuration is a computer monitor, keyboard and mouse, and a case that houses the main components of the PC, namely the power supply, motherboard, hard drive, optical drive, and previously the floppy drive.</string>
    <string name="hclcert">HCSE is the career-oriented software engineering course from HCL CDC.The course imparts a right blend of hands-on practices and theoretical knowledge.The course meticulously trains you in an array of Java and Android Track.</string>
    <string name="linux">Linux is a computer operating system assembled under the model of free- and open-source software development and distribution.</string>
    <string name="microsoft">HCL CDC offers hardware courses that provide students with complete insights for the hardware and networking concepts. The course can be taken up on the line of Microsoft technology.</string>
    <string name="networking">In the world of computers, networking is the practice of linking two or more computing devices together for the purpose of sharing data. Networks are built with a mix of computer hardware and computer software.</string>
    <string name="newadd">New additions to keep you updated with the latest happening and technologies around the globe.</string>
    <string name="redhat">HCL CDC offers hardware courses that provide students with complete insights for the hardware and networking concepts. The course can be taken up on the line of RED HAT technology.</string>
    <string name="win">Windows is Microsoft flagship operating system, the de facto standard for home and business computers. This GUI-based operating system was introduced in 1985 and has been released in many versions since then.</string>
    <string name="andjava">The Java platform, at its core, is a way of computing that is based on the power of networks and the idea that the same software should run on different kinds of computers, consumer gadgets and other devices. Android is the king of the mobile domain in all fields imaginable. It\'s the most flexible operating system when it comes to emulating various legacy hardware and software.</string>
   
    <string-array name="softwarecourse">
    	<item>"Select One"</item>
         <item >"Adv. Java"</item>
         <item >"Android with Java"</item>
         <item >"Android"</item>
         <item >"ASP.NET"</item>
         <item >"C"</item>
         <item >"CJava"</item>
         <item >"C++"</item>
         <item >"Database"</item>
         <item >"DotNET"</item>
         <item >"Java"</item>
         <item >"Lamp"</item>
         <item >"MS Office"</item>        
         <item >"PHP"</item>
         <item >"SQL"</item>
         <item >"VB.NET"</item>
    </string-array>
   
   <string-array name="hardwarecourse">
    	<item>"Select One"</item>
       <item >"Desktop"</item>
       <item >"Electronics"</item>
       <item >"HCL-Certified"</item>
       <item >"Linux/Administration"</item>
       <item >"Microsoft"</item>
       <item >"Networking"</item>
       <item >"New Additions"</item>
       <item >"Red Hat"</item>
       <item >"Windows"</item>
      
       
       </string-array>
       
   <string-array name="industcourse">
       <item>"Select One"</item>
       <item >"Non IT"</item>
        </string-array>
        
   <string-array name="othercourse">
       <item>"Select One"</item>
       <item >"Project Training"</item>
        </string-array>
       
   <string name="spintitle">Select Course</string>
   <string-array name="statearray">
       <item>"Select State"</item>
        <item >"Andhra Pradesh"</item>
        <item >"Assam"</item>
        <item >"Bihar"</item>
        <item >"Chandighar"</item>
        <item >"Delhi"</item>
        <item >"Gujarat"</item>
        <item >"Haryana"</item>
        <item >"Jharkhand"</item>
        <item >"Madhya Pradesh"</item>
        <item >"Maharashtra"</item>
        <item >"Orissa"</item>
        <item >"Punjab"</item>
        <item >"Rajasthan"</item>
        <item >"Tamil Nadu"</item>
        <item >"Uttar Pradesh"</item>                     
   </string-array>
   
   
   <string-array name="andhraarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Hyderabad-Tolichowak"</item>
   </string-array>
   
   <string-array name="asamarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Guwahati"</item>
   </string-array>
   
   <string-array name="bihararray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Purnea"</item>
   </string-array>
   
   <string-array name="chandiarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Chandigarh"</item>
   </string-array>
   
   <string-array name="delhiarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Munrika"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Preet vihar"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC South Extension"</item>
   </string-array>
   
    <string-array name="gujarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Ahmedabad Ashram Road"</item>
   </string-array>
   
     <string-array name="haryaarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Gurgaon"</item>
   </string-array>
   
      <string-array name="jhararray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Jamshedpur"</item>
   </string-array>
   
       <string-array name="mparray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Bhopal"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Navlakha"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Indore"</item>
   </string-array>
    
     <string-array name="mahaarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Karad"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Pune"</item>
   </string-array>
   
      <string-array name="orrisaarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Bhubaneswar-Shaheed Nagar new"</item>
   </string-array>
   
      <string-array name="punjabarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Ludhiana"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Mohali"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Patiala"</item>
   </string-array>
   
         <string-array name="rajarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Ajmer"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Jaipur"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Jodhpur"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Udaipur"</item>
   </string-array>
   
    <string-array name="tamilarray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Chennai Anna nagar"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Chennai Purasawalkam"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Chennai Tambaram"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Chennai Velachery"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Combatore Avinashi Road"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Combatore Gandhi Puram"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Erode"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Namakkal"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Trichy"</item>
   </string-array>   
   
     <string-array name="uparray">
   <item >"HCL CDC Allahabad"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Ghaziabad"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Kanpur"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Lucknow"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Noida"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Raebareli"</item>
   <item >"HCL CDC Varanasi Maldahiya"</item>
   </string-array>
   
     <string-array name="courses">
    	<item>"Select Course"</item>
         <item >"Adv. Java"</item>
         <item >"Android with Java"</item>
         <item >"Android"</item>
         <item >"ASP.NET"</item>
         <item >"C"</item>
         <item >"CJava"</item>
         <item >"C++"</item>
         <item >"Database"</item>
         <item >"DotNET"</item>
         <item >"Java"</item>
         <item >"Lamp"</item>
         <item >"MS Office"</item>        
         <item >"PHP"</item>
         <item >"SQL"</item>
         <item >"VB.NET"</item>
         <item >"Desktop"</item>
      	 <item >"Electronics"</item>
       	<item >"HCL-Certified"</item>
       <item >"Linux/Administration"</item>
       <item >"Microsoft"</item>
       <item >"Networking"</item>
       <item >"New Additions"</item>
       <item >"Red Hat"</item>
       <item >"Windows"</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
